# DWI PUTRA BAYU OKTANTYO

PROFILE

Experienced Operational Specialist with a demonstrated history of working in the computer software industry. I am skilled in office administration, data entry, web designer and graphic design. Strong information technology professional focused in Computer / Information Technology Administration.



- Zamrud VI Street Block A-7 No 5 Kembangan, Jakarta Barat
- dwiputrabayu19@gmail.com
- +62 89604333574

# EDUCATION BACKGROUND

#### **SDN 08 PAGI**

2003 - 2009

**SMPN 134 MERUYA** 

2009 - 2012

#### **SMA YADIKA 3 BANTEN**

SOCIAL SCIENCE AVERAGE VALUE (81.2/10) 2012 - 2015



# SPECIALIZATIONS

- Microsoft Office Word, Exel, Power Point
- Graphic Design
- Web Design
- Social Media
- Installation Computer

#### WORK EXPERIENCE

#### **SHOPEE** (Freelance)

RIDER 10

10 DESEMBER 2020 - 15 DESEMBER 2020

- Deliver package in a timely manner
- Deliver consumer packages without slightest damage
- Make sure the item matches the shipping address

## **GORGA GROUP**

WEB DESIGN

JUNE 2020 - SEPTEMBER 2020

- Create and define web display design
- Create an animation on the website
- Make the website responsive

#### TRAINING

#### HTML, CSS & JAVASCRIPT

PROGATE JUNE 2020 - SEPTEMBER 2020

DATE: 17 MARCH 2021 - 21 APRIL 2021

## LANGUAGE

- INDONESIA
- ENGLISH